Hubbell Trading Post records, 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sub-group II: Vendor Files, 1890-1962
  - Series II: Intra-Post Vendors, 1890-1962
    - T.S. Hubbell, Santa Monica. 1944-1947, 1949 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Keams Canyon. 1903-1908 (Box 257, Folder 4-5)
    - Keams Canyon: intra-post/off-post sales/purchases parts 1-3. January 11, 1913-July 1, 1909 (Box 257, Folder 6-8)
    - Keams Canyon: parts 4-7. June 29, 1909-February 7, 1908 (Box 258, Folder 1-4)
    - Keams Canyon. 1909-1911 (Box 258, Folder 5-7)
    - Keams Canyon. 1912-1918 (Box 259, Folder 1-7)
    - Long Beach. 1921 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Nakai Tso. 1933-1939 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Navajo Rug shop, Phoenix. 1947-1950 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Nazini. 1915-1918 (Box 260, Folder 4-6)
    - Oraibi. 1905-1913 (Box 260, Folder 7-10)
    - Oraibi. 1-14-1924 (Box 261, Folder 1-8)
    - Oraibi. 1925-1926 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: delivery receipts. December-January 1926 (Box 262, Folder 2-3)
    - Oraibi. 1927 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: delivery orders. 1927 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: off-post/intra-post invoice carbons. December-May 1929 (Box 262, Folder 6-7)
    - Oraibi: off-post/intra-post invoice carbons. April-January 1929 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: original invoices, mostly with Greasewood. 1930 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: off-post/intra-post invoice carbons. December-January 1930 (Box 263, Folder 3-5)
    - Oraibi: carbons with Greasewood. 1930 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: original invoices with Greasewood. 1931 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: off-post/intra-post invoice carbons. December-January 1931 (Box 264, Folder 1-3)
    - Oraibi. 1932-1934 (Box 264, Folder 4-6)
    - Oraibi: carbon invoice book including check deposits, part 1. December 31, 1934-May 6, 1933 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: carbon copy invoice book, parts 2-6. (Box 265, Folder 1-5)
    - Oraibi. 1935 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: carbons. 1935 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi. 1936 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: carbons. 1936 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi. 1937-1939 (Box 266, Folder 5-7)
    - Oraibi: "C" invoice book, carbons, off-post/intra-post, parts 1-5. November 29, 1941-November 25, 1939 (Box 267, Folder 1-5)
    - Oraibi: "A" invoices, statements of charges with Big Mountain. 1940 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: "A" invoices, statements of charges. 1941 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi. 1942-1943, 1948, 1950 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: delivery order books. July 10, 1941-December 9, 1941 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: delivery order books. April 2, 1943-October 23, 1943 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: delivery order books. August 3, 1935-October 31, 1945 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: delivery order books. April 14, 1946-January 16, 1947 (Box 268, Folder 6-7)
    - Pinon. 1917-1922 (Box 268, Folder 8-9)
    - Pinon: shipping order books. October 26, 1920-September 28, 1923 (Box 268, Folder 10-13)
    - Pinon. 1923-1950 (Box 269, Folder 1-2)
    - St. Michaels: Jim C. Karigan (relationship to Hubbell enterprises is not known). 1915 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Sheep Springs. 1915-1918 (Box 269, Folder 4-7)
    - Tenebito. 1923-1941 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Winslow. 1924-1928 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: delivery orders, off-post/intra-post. 1928 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: delivery receipts, off-post/intra-post. 1929 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Winslow. 1930 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: delivery orders. 1930 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: delivery receipts, off-post/intra-post. 1930 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Winslow. 1931 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: delivery orders. 1931 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: delivery receipts, off-post/intra-post. 1931 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: delivery orders. 1932 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: delivery receipts, off-post/intra-post. 1932 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Winslow. 1932-1933 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: delivery orders. 1933 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: delivery receipts, off-post/intra-post. 1933 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Winslow. January-July 1934 (Box 272, Folder 1-7)
    - Winslow. August-December 1934 (Box 273, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow: delivery receipt book, off-post/intra-post. November 16, 1934-January 1, 1935 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Winslow. January-May 1935 (Box 274, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow. June-December 1935 (Box 275, Folder 1-3)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. January-June 1935 (Box 275, Folder 4-9)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. July-December 1935 (Box 276, Folder 1-6)
    - Winslow: credit memo book. November 19, 1934-March 31, 1936 (Box 276, Folder 7-12)
    - Winslow. January-February 1936 (Box 276, Folder 13-14)
    - Winslow. March -June 1936 (Box 277, Folder 1-4)
    - Winslow. July-November 1936 (Box 278, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow. December 1936 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. January-October 1936 (Box 279, Folder 2-11)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. November-December 1936 (Box 280, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: credit memo book. March 1, 1936-January 18, 1937 (Box 280, Folder 3-9)
    - Winslow. January-June 1937 (Box 280, Folder 10-13)
    - Winslow. July-December 1937 (Box 281, Folder 1-6)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. January-February 1937 (Box 281, Folder 7-8)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. March -December 1937 (Box 282, Folder 1-10)
    - Winslow: credit memo books. January 18, 1937-February 26, 1938 (Box 282, Folder 11-16)
    - Winslow. January 1938 (Box 282, Folder 17)
    - Winslow. February-November 1938 (Box 283, Folder 1-7)
    - Winslow. December 1938 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: "W" invoices. January-December 1938 (Box 284, Folder 2-10)
    - Winslow: credit memo books. February 29, 1938-July 30, 1938 (Box 284, Folder 11-13)
    - Winslow. January 1939 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Winslow. February-June 1939 (Box 285, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow. July-November 1939 (Box 286, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow. December 1939-May 1940 (Box 287, Folder 1-6)
    - Winslow. June-December 1940 (Box 288, Folder 1-7)
    - Winslow. January-September 1941 (Box 289, Folder 1-9)
    - Winslow. October 1941-December 1942 (Box 290, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow: credit memo book. July 8, 1942-February 15, 1943 (Box 290, Folder 6-9)
    - Winslow. January-June 1943 (Box 290, Folder 10-13)
    - Winslow. July-December 1943 (Box 291, Folder 1-6)
    - Winslow: credit memo books. February 2, 1943-December 30, 1943 (Box 291, Folder 7-19)
    - Winslow: delivery orders. 1943-1944 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Winslow. January-May 1944 (Box 292, Folder 2-6)
    - Winslow. June-December 1944 (Box 293, Folder 1-7)
    - Winslow: credit memo books. March 30, 1944-August 31, 1944 (Box 294, Folder 1-8)
    - Winslow. January-October 1945 (Box 294, Folder 9-12)
    - Winslow. November-December 1945 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with all posts, "B" invoice register. December 1, 1946-November 28, 1947 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Winslow with Big Mountain. 1946 (Box 295, Folder 3-4)
    - Winslow: with frontier trading post. 1946 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Ganado. 1946 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., "Mtr" invoices. December 2, 1946-November 4, 1949 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., charges. December-January 1946 (Box 296, Folder 2-4)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., credits. December-January 1946 (Box 296, Folder 5-6)
    - Winslow: with T.S. Hubbell. 1946 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, invoices. 1946 (Box 296, Folder 8-9)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, charges/credits. 1946 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso. 1946 (Box 297, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, invoices. 1946 (Box 297, Folder 3-4)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, charges. 1946 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, credits. 1946 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, invoices. 1946 (Box 298, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: with Pinon charges. 1946 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with Pinon credits. 1946 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Tenebito. 1946 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: various accounts, credits. 1946 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. 1946-1947 (Box 298, Folder 7-11)
    - Winslow: with Big Mountain, "R" invoices. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Big Mountain, charges/credits. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with Big Mountain, delivery statement. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with Frontier. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Ganado. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 5-8)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: with T.S. Hubbell. 1947 (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "R" invoices. 1947 (Box 300, Folder 1-4)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "W" invoices. 1947 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, charges/credits. 1947 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, "R" invoices. 1947 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, charges/credits. 1947 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, "R" invoices. January-May 1947 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, "R" invoices.. June-December 1947 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with with Oraibi, charges/credits. 1947 (Box 301, Folder 2-5)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, "R" Invoices. 1947 (Box 301, Folder 6-7)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, charges/credits. January-June 1947 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, charges/credits. July-December 1947 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Tenebito, "R" invoices. 1947 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with Tenebito, charges/credits. 1947 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. 1947 (Box 302, Folder 4-18)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. July 29, 1947-January 3, 1948 (Box 303, Folder 1-15)
    - Winslow: with "B" invoice register. May 15, 1958-October 2, 1951 (Box 303, Folder 16)
    - Winslow: with Big Mountain, "R"/"W" invoices. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Big Mountain, charges/credits. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with Frontier. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "R" invoices. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "W" invoices. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, charges/invoices. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "R" invoices. 1948 (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "R" invoices (#901-1745, #10-88). 1948 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "W" invoices. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 2-3)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, charges/credits. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Navajo Rug Shop, Phoenix. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, "R"/"W" invoices. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, charges/credits. 1948 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: with Pinon. 1948 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Tenebito. 1948 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with various accounts. 1948 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. January 3-June 17, 1948 (Box 306, Folder 4-19)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. June 15-December 28, 1948 (Box 307, Folder 1-16)
    - Winslow: with all posts, "W" invoices (#309-197, #600-449). 1949 (Box 307, Folder 17)
    - Winslow: with all posts, "W" invoices (#1525-601, #1-87). 1949 (Box 308, Folder 1-4)
    - Winslow: with Frontier. 1949 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "B" invoices, "R" invoices (#95-592). 1949 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "R" invoices (#606-1509, #13-66). 1949 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, charges/credits. 1949 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., invoices. 1949 (Box 309, Folder 3-6)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., "B" invoices, credit memos. 1949 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with T.S. Hubbell. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "R" invoices. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 2-3)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, charges/credits. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, "R" invoices, delivery statements. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, charges/credits. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with Navajo Rug Shop, Phoenix. 1949 (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, "R" invoices. 1949 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, charges/credits. 1949 (Box 311, Folder 2-3)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, "B" invoice, "R" invoices. January-June 1949 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, "R" invoices. July-December 1949 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, charges/credits. July-December 1949 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: miscellaneous credit memos. 1949 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: delivery statement books. January 28-November 2, 1949 (Box 312, Folder 3-11)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. January-June 10, 1949 (Box 312, Folder 12-18)
    - Winslow: with all posts, "W" invoices (#87-1148). 1950 (Box 313, Folder 1-4)
    - Winslow: with all posts, "W" invoices (#1149-1506). 1950 (Box 314, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: with Frontier. 1950 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "R" invoices. 1950 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, charges/credits. 1950 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, delivery statements. 1950 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co. 1950 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, "W" invoices, "R" invoices. January-November 1950 (Box 314, Folder 8-9)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon, charges/credits. 1950 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, "R" invoices. 1950 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso, charges/credits. 1950 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: with Navajo Rug Shop, Phoenix. 1950 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, "R" invoices. January-November 1950 (Box 315, Folder 5-6)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi, charges/credits. January-November 1950 (Box 315, Folder 7-8)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, "R" invoices. January-November 1950 (Box 316, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: with Pinon, charges/credits. 1950 (Box 316, Folder 3-4)
    - Winslow: with credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. January 25-March 13, 1950 (Box 316, Folder 5-6)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "R" invoices, credits/charges. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: with Ganado, "W" invoices. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: with L.H.Motor Co. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - Winslow: with Nakai Tso. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Winslow: with Oraibi. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Winslow: with Pinon. 1951 (Box 316, Folder 13)
    - Winslow: delivery statement books. January 4-August 30, 1951 (Box 317, Folder 1-8)
    - Winslow: with Ganado. 1952 (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., "B"/"Mtr" invoices. January-June 1952 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: with L.H. Motor Co., charges/credits. April-August 1952 (Box 318, Folder 2-3)
    - Winslow: with Marble Canyon. 1952 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: credit memo books, off-post/intra-post. May 31-July 26, 1952 (Box 318, Folder 5-6)
- Sub-group III: Business Books and Records, 1882-1967
  Contains all the books and records in which the ordinary flow of business is accounted for on a day-to-day basis: daybooks, cashbooks, individual accounts (ledgers, ledger sheets), journals, daily sheets, etc.
  - Series I: Daily Records, 1882-1967
    - Big Mountain: yearly reports, monthly sheets. 1940-1945 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Big Mountain: sheep and cattle. 1940-1941 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Big Mountain: kitchen accounts, "labor bills," "meat bills," "gifts," "water & wood," wool sacks, Indian accounts. 1940-1942 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets, Indian accounts, sheep, pawn, cattle. 1913-1916 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets, Indian accounts. 1914-1916 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets, shipments (beef, wool, hides, other). 1914-1918 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets, sheep and cattle. 1916 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets. March 26-July 5, 1918 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Black Mountain: monthly sheets, accounts (various). 1919-1920 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Black Mountain: cash journal (p.17-27), journal (p.28-130), cash (p.29-131), wool (p.266), rugs (p.271-281), trial balances (p.250-256). 1922-1923 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Black Mountain: accounts (various), Indian accounts. 1923 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Black Mountain: sheep, dipping records. 1937 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Black Mountain: monthly sheets, daily sheets (part 1). 1931-1934 (Box 320, Folder 6-7)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 2). June-December 1934 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 3). January-May 1935 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 4). June-December 1935 (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 5). January-June 1936 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 6). July-December 1936 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 7). January-May 1937 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Black Mountain: daily sheets (part 8). June-November 1937 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Canyon Diablo: daily sheets, Indian accounts, accounts (various). 1930-1931 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Diablo: half-year summary, daily sheets with weekly summaries, Chinle (Indian and various accounts), pawn, "list of pawned goods on hand, January 10, 1887," shipments ("received by Lyman Parker," and "Blankets shipped to S.E. Day"). 1886-1931 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Chinle: various accounts, pawn (p.38-41), "Bets on Horse Race," "For trips to Ganado and hire," and list of Indian words (p.207-209). 1886-1887 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Chinle: daybook, miscellaneous. 1917 (Volume 322)
    - Cornfields: cashbook, various accounts. 1914-1918 (Volume 323)
    - Cornfields: various accounts, daybook (p.17-92), cashbook (p.253-283), pawn (p.1-15). 1898-1902 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Cornfields: daybook, shipments, accounts, Indian accounts. 1900-1903 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Cornfields: accounts (various), shipments to Ganado (p.36-56), shipments from Ganado (p.26-31), sales (p.1-23). 1908-1909 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Cow Springs: daily sheets (p.16-61), various and Indian accounts, shipments (p.6-14, 82-92), rugs, miscellaneous. 1922-1926 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Cow Springs: daily sheets (p.1-8), various accounts, sheep (p.100-112). 1935 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Dam Store: cash (p.2-33). 1916-1917 (Box 325)
    - Dam Store: various and Indian accounts. 1917-1919 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Dam Store: various and Indian accounts. 1917-1921 (Box 325, Folder 2-4)
    - Dam Store: daybook (p.3-292), wood (p.296, 294), borrow & loan (p.296). 1918-1920 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Dam Store: various accounts, "copy of bills sent to J.L. Hubbell," (p. 303-316). 1920-1921 (Box 325)
    - Frontier Trading Post: rugs (p.1-19), jewelry (p.125), Mexican rugs (p.135), various accounts (rugs, p. 1-27, 50, 55, 57). 1945-1950 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Gallup: sheep (sent to herd, bought), "Order from Ganado, Mission, Care, Haulers," (p. 19-27). 1922-1923 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Gallup: daily sheets, daybook-journal (p.124-295). 1926-1927 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Gallup: journal sheets. 1930 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Gallup: daybook (p. 1-70 missing). 1931-1932 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: cover (J.L. Hubbell/Pueblo Col. Store/1883), various accounts, miscellaneous. 1882-1883 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: front past-in (Chas. Hubbell,/Ganado/Arizona/November 22, 1883), front flyleaf (Charles Hubbell/Ganado/Arizona/Apache Co/Opened Store the fifth day/of April 1883), various accounts, sheep and goats, wool (black and white), miscellaneous. 1883-1884 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: various accounts, monthly sheets. 1884-1890 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: inside front flyleaf (C.N. Cotton/Ganado/Arizona/ Jany 1, 1887/Mrs. & Miss Burton/ no.2--1 stone/Mrs. Baird/no.3--/Miss Hutchins), various accounts, Indian accounts, "Record of A/C with Silversmiths (p.402-405)," and "Record of C'tle due by Indians (p.426-427)." 1887-1905 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: cashbook (p.19-67), shipments, wool, and pelts (p.3-17). 1890 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: cashbook (p.150-161), journal (p.164-169). 1890 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: front flyleaf (C.N. Cotton/Ganado/Arz/Jany 1st 1887), daybook (p.1-299), "Amount flour at Lynches (p.300-3001)," "Rest of Horses at San Benito (p.304-305)." 1887-1890 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.1-2, 19-496), Indian accounts, "Cattle in the herd (p.499). 1883-1899 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: cashbook. September 1, 1890-July 29, 1892 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.1-233), list of supplies (p.236-237), list of horses (p.238).. May 8, 1890-May 25, 1893 (Volume 329)
    - Ganado: cashbook (p.478-495), journal (p.2-136). 1890-1892 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: cashbook. September 1, 1892-December 31, 1901 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: journal. September 1, 1892-September 30, 1900 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: various accounts. 1890-1892 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, "Record of Ctle due from the year 1900 (p.297-300)," "List of freighters--for Gov flour." 1900-1905 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: shipments(p.1-14, 501-526). 1887-1890 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: shipments, wool, goats, sheep, other. February 22, 1891-January 4, 1908 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.297-292), daily sheets (p.35-273, 1-34 missing). 1907 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: daybook, cover (Blotter/Jan 1st 1900 to/Dec 31st 1901), "Sent to Albuquerque January 17, 1900 (p.295)," "Bkts to Albuquerque (p.296-297)," orders (p.298). January 1,1900-December 31, 1901 (Volume 333)
    - Ganado: daybook. January 1, 1902-September 5, 1903 (Volume 334)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.75-300), journal (p.1-74). 1900-1904 (Volume 335)
    - Ganado: daybook. November 21, 1904-June 9, 1906 (Volume 336)
    - Ganado: various accounts. 1892-1901 (Volume 337)
    - Ganado: daily sheets. December 1, 1909-October 24, 1910 (Volume 338)
    - Ganado: cashbook. January 1, 1902-February 3,1912 (Volume 339)
    - Ganado: various accounts. 1902-1907 (Volume 340)
    - Ganado: index to previous volume. 1902-1907 (Volume 341)
    - Ganado: various accounts. 1908-1910 (Volume 342)
    - Ganado: index to previous volume. 1908-1910 (Volume 343)
    - Ganado: Indian Accounts. 1900-1902 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: Indian Accounts. 1902-1911 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: Indian Accounts. 1905-1908 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: Indian Accounts, merchandise, blankets, household, etc. 1906-1912 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: Indian Accounts. 1907-1910, 1912 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, miscellaneous. 1908-1911 (Volume 345)
    - Ganado: journal. January 1, 1902-December 18, 1907 (Volume 346)
    - Ganado: journal. December 19, 1907-November 30, 1910 (Volume 347)
    - Ganado: shipments. January 21, 1908-January 1, 1913 (Volume 348)
    - Ganado: shipments. July 2, 1907-May 8, 1909 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: shipments. May 10, 1909-December 14, 1910 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daybook. June 1, 1910-August 31, 1912 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: daybook. September 1, 1912-December 15, 1913 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: daybook, miscellaneous material. December 1913-May 18, 1917 (Box 349, Folder 5)